Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 5 and District 5 Locals, 1936-1983 UE.4.1.5
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 5, 1.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism with District 1 Minutes Excerpt, January 20, 1944; 9.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - C.S. Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, Canadian Locomotive and Montreal, January 26, 1944; 1.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Supplies, February 15, 1944; 2.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, February 16, 1944; 3.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, March 6, 1944; 4.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding War Bonds, March 7, 1944; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Incentive and War Labor Board, March 21, 1944; 6.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Organization and War Labor Board, March 23, 1944; 7.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Organization and War Labor Board, May 6, 1944; 8.
    - Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Finances, May 15, 1944; 9.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, May 19, 1944; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Contracts, Seniority, and GE Organization, June 19, 1944; 11.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Canadian Visit, June 2, 1944; 12.
    - Jackson to District 5 Locals Regarding Hours, Vacations, and Political Action with Regulations and June 23, 1944, Jackson Letter to Industry & Labor Board, June 24, 1944; 13.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Canadian Visit, July 13, 1944; 14.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, July 15, 1944; 15.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances and Canadian Visit, July 31, 1944; 16.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - C.S. Jackson to David Scribner Regarding Finances, August 2, 1944; 1.
    - Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 24, 1944; 2.
    - Jackson to Frederick Livingston Regarding Staff Finances, September 25, 1944; 3.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Organization, Unemployment, and Staff Finances, October 4, 1944; 4.
    - Jackson to Livingston Regarding Staff Member, October 7, 1944; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Philco Organization, Toronto, and Unemployment, October 10, 1944; 6.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 3, 1944; 7.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Political Action, Canadian Visit, and Canadian Congress of Labour, November 7, 1944; 8.
    - Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Political Action, November 8, 1944; 9.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Local 512, December 5, 1944; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding CCL and London Conference, December 13, 1944; 11.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding CCL and World Trade Union Conference, December 29, 1944; 12.
    - Jackson to Ray Klausner Regarding London Conference, January 3, 1945; 13.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding London Conference and Finances, January 19, 1945; 14.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding London Conference and USSR with A Trade Union's Views on Belgium and Holland, March 2, 1945; 15.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding USSR Trade Unions, March 2, 1945; 16.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Westinghouse Contract, March 14, 1945; 17.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - C.S. Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, March 22, 1945; 1.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Collective Bargaining, March 27, 1945; 2.
    - Jackson to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, April 9, 1945; 3.
    - Jackson to Tom Wright Regarding Radio Broadcasts and Political Action, April 18, 1945; 4.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Address, April 27, 1945; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding International Labor Organization with ILO Letter and Statement, May 3, 1945; 6.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 9, 1945; 7.
    - Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations and Inter-union Rivalry, July 11, 1945; 8.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour, World Federation of Trade Unions, CIO, and Organization, July 24, 1945; 9.
    - Jackson to PAC Committees Regarding WFTU and CCL, July 24, 1945; 10.
    - Jackson to A.R. Mosher Regarding WFTU and CCL, July 23, 1945; 11.
    - Jackson to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, September 28, 1945; 12.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding International Association of Machinists, Organization, and Montreal, September 28, 1945; 13.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding CCL and WFTU, October 10, 1945; 14.
    - Jackson to James Matles Regarding New York Visit, October 27, 1945; 15.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Organization, October 24, 1945; 16.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Canadian Visit, October 26, 1945; 17.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - C.S. Jackson to James Matles Regarding Imperial Optical Strike, Westinghouse Hamilton, and Canadian Congress of Labour, November 8, 1945; 1.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding UE News, November 21, 1945; 2.
    - Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Social Work, November 26, 1945; 3.
    - Jackson to Ray Klausner Regarding New York Visit, November 29, 1945; 4.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Faultless Caster, November 29, 1945; 5.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding United Auto Workers, December 18, 1945; 6.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding GE, General Motors, and Westinghouse Strikes, United Steelworkers of America, and Union Shop, January 31, 1946; 7.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Rogers Tubes and Phillips Electric Strikes, March 15, 1946; 8.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding CCL and Phillips Electric Strike, April 1, 1946; 9.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding New York Visit, April 16, 1946; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Collective Bargaining and USWA, May 7, 1946; 11.
    - Jackson to Klausner Regarding New York Visit, May 14, 1946; 12.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Collective Bargaining, USWA, and National Carbon Organization, June 7, 1946; 13.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Westinghouse and GE Strikes, July 5, 1946; 14.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding USWA and Westinghouse Strikes, July 17, 1946; 15.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Strikes and House of Commons Industrial Relations Committee with Statement, July 1946; 16.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Strike, August 6, 1946; 17.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Strikes and Per Capita, August 13, 1946; 18.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - C.S. Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Strikes, United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, and Canadian Congress of Labour, August 19, 1946; 1.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Strikes, USWA Inter-union Rivalry, and United Auto Workers, August 21, 1946; 2.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Phillips Electric Contract and Hours, August 27, 1946; 3.
    - Jackson to James Matles Regarding Strikes, Inter-union Rivalry, and USWA, September 16, 1946; 4.
    - Jackson to David Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, September 17, 1946; 5.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry and RCA Montreal, October 11, 1946; 6.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 19, 1946; 7.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding RCA Montreal and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, October 26, 1946; 8.
    - Jackson to Joseph Dermody Regarding Publicity and Mailing List, December 2, 1946; 9.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Films, December 23, 1946; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 26, 1946; 11.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Strikes, Organization, Inter-union Rivalry, IBEW, RCA, Factionalism, and Finances, December 26, 1946; 12.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, December 26, 1946; 13-14.
    - Jackson to Tom Wright Regarding Radio Broadcast, January 21, 1947; 15.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Local 507, January 25, 1947; 16.
    - Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 507 and Factionalism, January 30, 1947; 17.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Inflation and Inter-union Rivalry, March 7, 1947; 18.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 10, 1947; 19.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - C.S. Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Publicity, March 29, 1947; 1.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Radio Broadcasts, April 14, 1947; 2.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, May 30, 1947; 3.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 5, 1947; 4.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 13, 1947; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding GE Strike, Finances, Canadian Congress of Labour, and United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, June 12, 1947; 6.
    - Jackson to James Matles Regarding Staff Meetings and United Auto Workers, June 16, 1947; 7.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 20, 1947; 8.
    - Jackson to Ray Klausner Regarding New York Visit, June 23, 1947; 9.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, July 2, 1947; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 14, 1947; 11.
    - Jackson to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, July 28, 1947; 12.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 5, 1947; 13.
    - Jackson to David Scribner Regarding Immigration, November 25, 1947; 14.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding UE Constitution, GE Peterboro, and Factionalism, January 23, 1948; 15.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Allis Chalmers Rockfield Organization, March 18, 1948; 16.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Organization and Finances, March 29, 1948; 17.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Marshall Plan and Political Action, April 12, 1948; 18.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Factionalism, GE, Peterboro, USWA Inter-union Rivalry, English Electric, GE Organization, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Strike, and Rogers, May 3, 1948; 19.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - C.S. Jackson to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, May 10, 1948; 1.
    - Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Address Change, June 28, 1948; 2.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 8, 1948; 3.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Rogers Majestic Strike and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 16, 1948; 4.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Seamen Strike, August 5, 1948; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Travel Bans, August 18, 1948; 6.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Rogers Majestic Strike and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, August 19, 1948; 7.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding English Electric and United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, September 9, 1948; 8.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding English Electric and USWA Inter-union Rivalry, September 10, 1948; 9.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding English Electric and USWA Inter-union Rivalry, September 13, 1948; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding 1948 UE Convention, September 13, 1948; 11.
    - Jackson to A.R. Mosher Regarding 1948 UE Convention, CCL, and USWA Inter-union Rivalry, September 13, 1948; 12.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Rogers Strike and Travel Bans, September 13, 1948; 13.
    - Jackson to James Matles Regarding CCL, American Federation of Labor, Seamen Union Strike, Cooperative Commenwealth Federation, and United Auto Workers with October 18, 1948, Report on CCL Convention, October 19, 1948; 14.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - C.S. Jackson to Pat Conroy Regarding American Federation of Labor and United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry and Canadian Congress of Labour with November 26, 1948, A.R. Mosher Letter to Jackson, November 30, 1948; 1.
    - Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Sovreign Potteries, AFL Potters Inter-union Rivalry, USWA, and CCL, November 30, 1948; 2.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding CCL and Sovreign Potteries, December 8, 1948; 3.
    - Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, Finances, and District 5 Locals, December 8, 1948; 4.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding French Miners Union, December 10, 1948; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding International Woodworkers Association, CCL, and Independent Woodworkers with December 17, 1948, Mosher and Norman Dowd Letters and December 8, 1948, Philip Murray Letter, December 22, 1948; 6.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Organization and Dues, February 16, 1949; 7.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding World Federation of Trade Unions, February 16, 1949; 8.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Local 577, February 25, 1949; 9.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding WFTU and CCL, March 1, 1949; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding CCL, USWA Inter-union Rivalry, Wages, and Cooperation Common Federation, March 29, 1949; 11.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - C.S. Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Travel Bans, 1949 UE Convention, and Canadian Congress of Labour, April 2, 1949; 1.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Travel Bans and 1949 UE Convention, April 2, 1949; 2.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Literature, April 27, 1949; 3.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and CCL, April 27, 1949; 4.
    - Jackson to James Matles Regarding Per Capita and CCL, April 29, 1949; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding District Council, Factionalism, and CCL, May 2, 1949; 6.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Womens Conference, May 31, 1949; 7.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Travel Bans, June 6, 1949; 8.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding CCL and Inter-union Rivalry, June 14, 1949; 9.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding CCL and Inter-union Rivalry with Newspaper Clippings, June 21, 1949; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and CCL, June 21, 1949; 11.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding World Federation of Trade Unions and British Electrical Trade Unions, June 30, 1949; 12.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding CCL, Inter-union Rivalry, and Political Action, July 6, 1949; 13.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding WFTU, July 6, 1949; 14.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - C.S. Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding 1949 UE Convention, July 7, 1949; 1.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Travel Bans, July 7, 1949; 2.
    - Jackson to James Matles Regarding Factionalism and Travel Bans, August 13, 1949; 3.
    - Jackson to International Vice President Regarding Factionalism and GE Peterboro, August 17, 1949; 4.
    - Jackson to James Matles Regarding Unemployment and 1949 UE Convention, September 29, 1949; 5.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, CCL, Factionalism, and GE Peterboro, September 29, 1949; 6.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding 1949 UE Convention, Factionalism, and GE Peterboro, September 30, 1949; 7.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Factionalism, September 30, 1949; 8.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding 1949 UE Convention, Factionalism, and GE Peterboro, October 8, 1949; 9.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding World Federation Trade Unions and United Steelworkers of America with October 7, 1949, H. Jourdain Letter, October 11, 1949; 10.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Strikes, GE Peterboro, and Factionalism with Statement of the Joint Conference Board of the GE UE Locals, October 19, 1949; 11.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - C.S. Jackson to James Matles Regarding District Council, Factionalism, Westinghouse Strike, and Local 504 with A.R. Mosher Letter to Members of the Executive Board, December 5, 1949; 1.
    - Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour and Per Capita with December 5, 1949, Mosher Letter to Jackson, December 6, 1949; 2.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 12, 1949; 3.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 22, 1949; 4.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 17, 1950; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 19, 1950; 6.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, IUE Inter-union Rivalry, and GE Peterboro, February 8, 1950; 7.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 10, 1950; 8.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding GE Peterboro, Finances, and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 3, 1950; 9.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Contracts, GE, and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 27, 1950; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 4, 1950; 11.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, May 19, 1950; 12.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 19, 1950; 13.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Staff Finances and Members with Staff List, June 28, 1950; 14.
    - Jackson to Nat Spero Regarding 1950 UE Convention Report, August 4, 1950; 15.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding 1950 UE Convention and CCL, August 16, 1950; 16.
    - Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding District 5 Convention, September 13, 1950; 17.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - C.S. Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita and GE Organization, October 19, 1950; 1.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 22, 1951; 2.
    - Jackson to James Matles Regarding Canada Labour Relations Board, Canadian Seamen Union, Collective Bargaining, GE Organization, and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 24, 1951; 3.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, GE, and Organization, March 9, 1951; 4.
    - Jackson to David Ratner Regarding Finances, April 20, 1951; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding High Treason, April 30, 1951; 6.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Collective Bargaining, GE, Inter-union Rivalry, IUE, and CCL with Canadian Settlement, April 30, 1951; 7.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding European Trip, May 22, 1951; 8.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding GE Peterboro and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, May 25, 1951; 9.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - C.S. Jackson to James Matles Regarding GE Peterboro and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 26, 1951; 1.
    - Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 30, 1951; 2.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding 1951 UE Convention and Canadian Congress of Labour, September 10, 1951; 3.
    - Jackson to Mike Jimmez Regarding 1951 UE Convention, September 11, 1951; 4.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 26, 1951; 5.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, Novmeber 3, 1951; 6.
    - Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Canadian Visit and Women Conference, November 12, 1951; 7.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding Collective Bargaining, Westinghouse Strike, and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, April 18, 1952; 8.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding RCA Montreal, IBEW and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, July 1, 1952; 9.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Strikes and Nottal & Frontenac Tile, July 25, 1952; 10.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Local 519 and Inter-union Rivalry with IUE and IBEW, July 28, 1952; 11.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding District 5 Convention, October 3, 1952; 12.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Publicity, October 7, 1952; 13.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 513 and Catholic Syndicates Inter-union Rivalry, December 8, 1952; 14.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 513, Inter-union Rivalry, and Catholic Syndicates, December 11, 1952; 15.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 513, Inter-union Rivalry, and Catholic Syndicates with Resolutions, December 17, 1952; 16.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - C.S. Jackson to James Matles Regarding District 5 Locals and Per Capita, December 31, 1952; 1.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Publicity, January 7, 1953; 2.
    - Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding World Federation of Trade Unions, January 14, 1953; 3.
    - Jackson to Maltes Regarding GE Peterboro, IUE Inter-union Rivalry, Collective Bargaining, and GE, March 17, 1953; 4.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding GE, Peterboro, and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, May 8, 1953; 5.
    - Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding District 5 Locals, Inter-union Rivalry, and IUE, June 10, 1953; 6.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding District 5 Locals Convention with Statement and Revised Statement, September 14, 1953; 7.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding Attached Mailing List, January 26, 1953; 8.
    - Jackson to David Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, May 28, 1953; 9.
    - Jackson to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, July 23, 1953; 10.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding GE Collective Bargaining, November 16, 1953; 11.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - C.S. Jackson to James Matles Regarding District Convention, World Federation of Trade Unions, Collective Bargaining, and Political Action, November 24, 1954; 1.
    - Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Canadian Visit, December 23, 1954; 2.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding Canadian Visit, January 31, 1955; 3.
    - Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita and GE Collective Bargaining, March 25, 1955; 4.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Staff Finances, March 28, 1955; 5.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding Finances, April 29, 1955; 6.
    - Jackson to Fitzgerald Regarding UE Constitution with Proposed Constitutional Amendment, June 29, 1955; 7.
    - Jackson to Brother Regarding Collective Bargaining and Hours, July 4, 1955; 8.
    - Jackson to Emspak Regarding UE Constitution with Proposed Constitutional Amendment, August 9, 1955; 9.
    - Jackson to David Scribner Regarding UE Constitution, October 31, 1955; 10.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Outgoing Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - C.S. Jackson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Seamen Strike, n.d.; 1.
    - Jackson to Julius Emspak Regarding Strikes, n.d.; 2.
    - Jackson to James Matles Regarding Union Carbon Collective Bargaining, n.d.; 3.
    - Jackson to Matles Regarding GE Toronto Strike, n.d.; 4.
    - Jackson to Ferrant Electric Workers Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, n.d.; 5.
  - District 5 George Harris Incoming Correspondence, 1942-1952 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Peter Abbondi to George Harris Regarding Westinghouse Strike, July 12, 1946; 1.
    - Abbondi to Harris Regarding Westinghouse Strike with April 25, 1946, Gwilym Price Letter to Westinghouse Workers, July 12, 1946; 2.
    - Janet Barish to Harris Regarding Finances, May 5, 1945; 3.
    - Barish to Harris Regarding Staff Finances, July 14, 1947; 4.
    - Barish to Harris Regarding Strikes and Locals 443 and 504, March 31, 1952; 5.
    - Julius Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, March 2, 1942; 6.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, May 19, 1942; 7.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding District 5 Organization, June 25, 1942; 8.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, December 4, 1942; 9.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, January 5, 1943; 10.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Contracts, January 15, 1943; 11.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Charters, January 27, 1943; 12.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and District 5 Locals with Canadian Locals, February 4, 1943; 13.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, March 2, 1943; 14.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Mailing List, April 13, 1943; 15.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances, June 21, 1943; 16.
    - Emspak to Harris Regarding Finances and Mailing List, June 25, 1943; 17.